You won't last the night.
House of the Dead is a horror, action, thriller film directed by Uwe Boll.
On an island off the coast, a techno rave party attracts a diverse
group of college coeds and a Coast Guard officer.
Soon, they discover that their X-laced escapades are to be interrupted by zombies and monsters that
attack them on the ground, from the air, and in the sea, ruled by an evil entity.
Rudy, played by Jonathan Cherry.
Simon, played by Tyron Leitso.
Salish, played by Clint Howard.
Alicia, played by Ona Grauer.
Cynthia, played by Sonya Salomaa.
Casper, played by Ellie Cornell.
House of the Dead is a 2003 action horror film directed by Uwe Boll,
from a screenplay by Dave Parker and Mark Altman.
Based on The House of the Dead video game franchise, it stars Jonathan Cherry, Tyron
Leitso, Clint Howard, Ona Grauer, Ellie Cornell, and Jürgen Prochnow.
The film takes place on a fictional island infested by
zombies, forcing survivors to fight their way off.
Not a direct adaptation of the individual entries, Boll described
the film as a prequel to the original 1997 game.
House of the Dead was Boll's first film to be released
theatrically, in addition to his first video game adaptation.
Upon release, House of the Dead was universally panned by critics, giving Boll a
negative reputation that would continue throughout his career.
Commercially, the film grossed $13.8 million on a $12 million budget.
A direct-to-video sequel was released in 2006, with only Cornell returning.
House of the Dead was the last film released by Artisan
Entertainment, which merged into Lionsgate on December 15, 2003.
The film explores themes of island, rave, based on video game.
The tone is dark and intense.